<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">AnyTime Horoscope</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>
    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_registration_form">RegistrationForm</string>
    <string name="firstname">FirstName</string>
    <string name="first_name">First name</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last Name</string>
    <string name="title_activity_registration">RegistrationActivity</string>
    
    <!--zodiac strings-->
    
    <string name="Capricorn_Health">This year is going to be generally auspicious for professional life. You shall have to put in lot of efforts for getting progress in business. Thiose doping job shall be facing stress from their seniors. After the transit of Jupiter the time period shall turn favorable. The guidance of experience people shall help. You will devise new plans and new thinking the inclusion of which shall prove beneficial for the progress of your business. Those doing job are likely to get transferred to their place of choice.</string>
    <string name="Capricorn_Wealth">Financial condition would not be very good in this year. Therefore be cautious in your financial transactions. The combined impact of aspect of Saturn and Rahu on house of finance might not give very auspicious results therefore stay away from a risk taking situation in terms of financial investment especially. This year is not going to prove very auspicious for taking risks.</string>
    <!--<string name="Capricorn_Work">This year shall not be auspicious for your family life. Abstain from difference of opinion with family members. Take care of health of spouse, father and siblings. You are advised to have control on your language otherwise situation might get deteriorated. It would be better to maintain patience and enhance your tolerance while facing difficult and opposite situations.</string>-->
    <string name="Capricorn_Family">There are possibilities of child birth and your children would be doing reasonably well in their higher education. This year is beneficial for the happiness, education and destiny of children. The first half of the year is very auspicious for those who are expecting the birth of child in their family.</string>
    <string name="Capricorn_Children">This would be generally auspicious year for your health. Except few trivial problems the whole year shall turn out to be favorable for your health. Do not remain worried because of some financial issue. After 9th September your health might get deteriorated further. You are advised to work in a relaxed manner but don\'t be careless, lethargic and lazy otherwise your work area shall get affected negatively. Morning exercise can help you certainly. Try to achieve high life conditions by maintaining self-control in your daily routine and life style. Take healthy diet, keep yourself relaxed and have lot of rest</string>
    <string name="Capricorn_Career">he first half of the year shall be favorable for students but they would remain engaged in some unnecessary activities. You shall have to struggle very hard or getting success in your career. After 12th September you would be getting cooperation of experienced people. You would be getting new opportunities of employment. The new opportunities in career would enhance your reputation in society.</string>
    <string name="Capricorn_Travel">The possibilities of going on foreign journeys are there in this year. Those in job are likely to get transferred. Most of the times you might have to stay away from your motherland and house and it would be auspicious for you. You might go abroad for upgrading your education. The transit of jupiter in 9th house is giving indications of going on a pilgrimage.</string>
    <!--<string name="Capricorn_Regiousdeed">Jupiter would remain in 9th house in the first half of the year as a result of which you would be devoted to your Guru, God and religious traditions in the family. You would respect your Gurus and follow their preaching. You would be helping the poor every now and then. You would also perform some religious Yagya at home. 1. Worship Lord Shiva and chant Mhamrityunjay Mantra. 2. Offer red robe (Chola) to Lord Hanuman on Tuesday. 3. Donate blankets or black articles to poor and offer food.</string>-->

    
    
    
    <string name="Aries_Health">You shall be getting good results in terms of success in business. The aspect of Jupiter on house of profession is a good sign of progress on professional front. Your inflow of money would be stable. You are likely to get new source of income. Those in job are likely to get a better post of responsibility with transfer to a place of choice. The aspect of Jupiter on first house after 12th September shall give birth to new thinking line and plans.</string>
    <string name="Aries_Wealth">This is going to turn out to be an auspicious year for your financial progress. The transit of Jupiter on house of wealth indicates sudden financial gains. In addition to that you shall be able to get your blocked money too. Investment on some business would necessarily give good returns. You shall be spending money on religious journeys or other auspicious deeds. Your cooperative behavior shall prove beneficial for your progress in earning gains quickly.</string>
    <!--<string name="Aries_Work">This year shall bring in auspicious results for your family life in the first half of the year. There shall be an atmosphere of love, laughter, harmony and prosperity at home. You would be getting the cooperation of all family members. This is a highly auspicious time for your father. You would be worried about the health of your child. Newly married can expect the birth of a child. The latter half of the year is giving indications of difference of opinion with siblings.</string>-->
    <string name="Aries_Family">The first half of the year won\'t be auspicious for your children. The health and education of your children might get affected. Newly married females might face difficulties in conceiving. The pregnant women are advised to be cautious as there are possibilities of abortion. After 12th September your children shall be participating in social activities and their confidence shall get enhanced and in the process good result can be expected. Their hard work would help them do better in business.</string>
    <string name="Aries_Children">The health shall not be perfectly fine in the first half of the year.Therefore you need to look after your health. Be extra cautious if you are already suffering from some illness. The transit of Jupiter would be auspicious for your health in the latter half of the year. You would be mentally satisfied and have positive outlook. You would be improving your life style and eating habits to improve your health.</string>
    <string name="Aries_Career">The first half of the year is indicating success in competitive exams but you need to be focused but 5th house Rahu can create disinterestedness in education and for that reason the chances of success in competitive examination shall get decreased. The latter half of the year shall be more auspicious in this connection and you are likely to enroll yourself in a new course. You are likely to get new employment. There are probabilities of going away for carrying the pursuit of education.</string>
    <string name="Aries_Travel">You shall go on foreign journey in the beginning of the year. Be cautious of your luggage while going on journey as there is probability of theft etc. Those aspiring to get higher education might go abroad to achieve this objective. It is going to prove auspicious year for those who have greater inclination towards religious activities.</string>
    <!--<string name="Aries_Religiousdeed">You won\'t be very highly interested in religious activities especially in the first half of the year and might face obstacles in religious activities like pilgrimage or Yagya etc. 1. Donate useful articles made of iron on Saturday. 2. Donate grains in an Ashram and serve your parents. The weight of grains should be equal to your own body weight. 3. Donate coconut on Saturday.</string>-->

    
    
    
    
    <string name="Taurus_Health">You shall be doing something special in your business or job this year. It is a good time for your professional life. You shall be able to earn reputation and recognition for your work. You might face few difficulties while accomplishing your tasks. Your adversaries might try to create difficulties for you so do not trust anybody around you and work sensibly. Those doing job are likely to get transferred after 12th September.</string>
    <string name="Taurus_Wealth">Financial condition won\'t be very auspicious in this year. You won\'t be able to enhance your saving potential. Income and expenses shall increase in equal proportion. Money might get spent on the health of your parents. Your financial position should improve with the transit of Jupiter after 12th September.</string>
    <!--<string name="Taurus_Work">This year shall bring in mixed results for your family life. There is probability of difference of opinion with your spouse and with tensions in family atmosphere. The behavior of few family members won\'t be good. Therefore you need to enhance your power of tolerance so that you succeed in handling the adverse situations. The family atmosphere shall be better after the favorable transit of Jupiter. You need to look after the health of your parents.</string>-->
    <string name="Taurus_Family">Probabilities of progress of your children are indicated in the first half of this year. The combined influence of Jupiter and Saturn of transit on house of children is creating probabilities of child birth. This year is great for the education and progress of children. They shall earn reputation with their hard work.</string>
    <string name="Taurus_Children">he health shall remain generally good in this year.Except few trivial troubles the health shall remain good throughout the year. The aspect of Saturn on 5th house can create stomach related problems. Keep consulting your family physician. You need to be cautious and disciplined in your eating habits and if you are already suffering from some illness then you need to be more careful. The transit of Jupiter can enhance mental stress and you are advised to take care of your digestive system. Avoid spicy and oily food.</string>
    <string name="Taurus_Career">This year would bring in success in competitive examinations but you need to be focused. The latter half of the year shall be more auspicious in this connection and you are likely to enroll yourself in a new course. You are likely to get new employment.There are probabilities of going away for carrying the pursuit of education.</string>
    <string name="Taurus_Tarvel">You shall go on journeys in the latter half of the year. Those aspiring to get higher education might go abroad to achieve this objective in the latter half of the year.Business related journeys are also indicated.</string>
    <!--<string name="Religiousdeed">. Put a mark of Ashtagandha and Kesar everyday. 2. Chant Hanuman Chalisa daily. 3. Rotate a coconut on your head 7 times and then throw in running water.</string>-->

    
    
    
    
    
    
    <string name="Gemini_Health">By getting help and guidelines from experienced people you shall be able to bring improvement on your professional front. You would be enjoying the cooperation of your seniors and government officers. The transit of Jupiter shall prove auspicious for getting a bigger post of responsibility. Because of your success at work the number of opponents for you might increase and at that time you shall have to be cautious from secret enemies. They won\'t be able to harm you but give mental tensions. The first half the year is indicating sudden and good financial gains. The latter half of the year is giving indications of journeys related to work. You would be getting opportunity to work or associate yourself with a big organization and by working with it you would bring process in your work.</string>
    <string name="Gemini_Wealth">Financial condition would be average in this year. The aspect of Jupiter on 8th house can bring in gain of paternal property. There is probability of gain of land, house or vehicle in the first half of the year. The financial gains shall go on increasing because of which there shall be improvementin your financial position. Your some money might get spent in curing the health troubles of your family members. There is strong probability that your money might get spent on the health troubles of family members. Some auspicious celebration or marriage etc will also be the reason of increased expenses. After 12th September make investment on some property sensibly.</string>
    <!--<string name="Gemini_Work">This year shall bring in average results for your family life. The first half of the year is not auspicious for family atmosphere. There shall be difference of opinion with family members which would cause mental tensions to you. You are advised to speak sensibly otherwise tensions in relationship shall increase. The transit of jupiter shall improve family atmosphere by year end.</string>-->
    <string name="Gemini_Family">The first half of the year would be average for your children and they are advised to work sensibly with concentration for the up gradation of education. After 12th September you would be getting good news about the birth of child. This time period can also be considered suitable for conceiving. You can expect the birth of child at that time and in addition to that there would be probability of marriage of your elder child.</string>
    <string name="Gemini_Children">The health shall not remain fine in this year.You are likely to suffer from troubles like joint pain, weak digestion, and wind disease etc. Therefore try to improve the current condition by adopting a disciplined life style. Be disciplined in your eating habits and do not let yourself become victim of any mental tension or stress created by any opponent. Unnecessary tensions can affect your health negatively.</string>
    <string name="Gemini_Career">The first half of the year would be average for your children\'s education. You shall haveto work very hard for the progress of your career. In this year the new opportunities of career making shall get created. Third house can bring in the cooperation of experienced people as a result of which you can expect success in business and reputation in society. The transit of Jupiter in 5th house is indicating success in getting admission in an educational institutein the latter part of the year.</string>
    <string name="Gemini_Travel">This is a favorable time for going on journey.Those aspiring to get higher education might go abroad to achieve this objective in this year. Those in job are likely to get transferred to a place of choice. Jupiter\'s transit is indicating pilgrimages and journeys to places of historical importance by year end.</string>
    <!--<string name="Gemini_Religiousdeed">The aspect of Rahu on 9th house might create few obstacles in religious activities. You won\'t be much focused in activities like meditation, yagya and religious Anushthaan etc. 1. Donate iron articles black articles of use to poor people. 2. Flow one coconut in running water every month. 3. Donate Saptadhanya (7 grains) on Saturday. 4. Do Abhishekam of Shivling daily.</string>-->







    <string name="Cancer_Health">This year certainly you would be getting improvement in your business. The aspect of Jupiter on 7th house is auspicious for business. If you shall think of starting a business venture in partnership with somebody then it shall yield the desired results. You would be enjoying the co-operation of your seniors and government officers. There shall be an increase in your position by year end.</string>
    <string name="Cancer_Wealth">Financial condition would not be very good in this year. The second house Rahu can affect financial position badly. Therefore you are advised to be cautious in financial matters. Sudden unexpected expenses can spoil the shape of your budget. Therefore you are advised to save some money for your rainy days. The aspect of Saturn and Rahu on 8th house can create paternal property related troubles. There shall be slight changes with the transit of Jupiter which won\'t help much.</string>
    <!--<string name="Cancer_Work" tools:ignore="StringEscaping">This year shall not bring in good results for your family life. The second house Rahu can spoil family atmosphere which would result into difference of opinion with family members. You might have to go away from family people because of some reason. The behavior of few family members won't be good. Therefore you need to enhance your power of tolerance so that you succeed in handling the adverse situations. The transit of Rahu and Saturn in 8th house can affect your relations with in-lwas.</string>-->
    <string name="Cancer_Family">In this year you can expect growth in the career of your children. You shall be happy about the health, happiness and career of children especially the elder one. This year can be considered auspicious for the marriage of children. Advise them to be positive in their thinking. The time period in this year would bring in opportunities of sudden rise and recognition in career. An increase in their income can be expected</string>
    <string name="Cancer_Children">his year shall bring in mixed results for your health. The transit of Saturn in 6th house shall improve your health troubles. If you are suffering from some health trouble already then you might get rid of it this year. You might suffer from some mental tension on account of some financial issue or some problem created by opponent. Be cautious while going on journey. There is probability of accident and health problem.</string>
    <string name="Cancer_Career">This would be a very auspicious year for students. You shall be attaining success in competitive examinations so you are advised to get benefited from the favorable transit by putting in lot of efforts for the attainment of success. This would be a favorable year for students as the aspect of Jupiter on 9th house is highly favorable for higher education.</string>
    <string name="Cancer_Travel">The first half of the year is auspicious for journeys however, Jupiter\'s transit is indicating pilgrimages in the latter half of the year. The aspect of Saturn on 12th house is indicating abroad travel. You might go on foreign journeys on account of work/business. It is auspicious to change place for those in job or else it shall be easy to get transferred to a place of choice by the year end.</string>
    <!--<string name="Cancer_Religiousdeed">This year you would be inclined towards religious activities very strongly. You would be involved in philanthropic activities too. In addition to that you would be performing religious activities like Yagya, Anushthaan, Mata Ki Chowki, RamayanPaath or Bhagvat Katha etc. 1. Serve Hanumanji on Tuesday. 2. Donate green grass to cows. 3. Worship goddess Durga daily.</string>-->







    <string name="Leo_health">This year shall be generally auspicious for getting betterment in professional life. The aspect of Saturn on 7th house is giving sure indications of change in business. Those in job are likely to get promoted or transferred. The partnership would prove beneficial for you. During this time it shall prove beneficial beneficial to be confident. There is probability of some tensions from adversaries by the end of the year however; you would be able to get a solution for this type of problem.</string>
    <string name="Leo_Wealth">Financial condition would be good in the first half of the year. There is probability of getting new sources of income. The transit of jupiter shall increase saving potential and in addition to that there might remain the probability of gain of paternal property too. You would be making investment for starting a new venture. You would plan to invest on vehicle or property etc. You might renovate your old house or office. After 12th Sepotember you are advised not to make big investment in that venture where some kind of risk is involved otherwise you would be losing money.</string>
    <!--<string name="Leo_Work" tools:ignore="StringEscaping">This year shall be auspicious for your family life as the transit of Jupiter would prove highly auspicious for your family life. The number of family members shall increase. You are advised to be cautious about your relation with your in- laws.The behavior of few family members won't be good. Therefore you need to enhance your power of tolerance so that you succeed in handling the adverse situations</string>-->
    <string name="Leo_family">This year isaverage for the progress of your children. The aspect of Rahu on 5th house is not auspicious for the progress of your children. His education also might get affected. The pregnant females are advised to be cautious as the aspect of Rahu can create the probabilities of abortion. After 9th September the auspicious time period can be considered as an auspicious Muhurat for conceiving.</string>
    <string name="Leo_Children">This year is not favorable for your health. The Transit of Rahu on Lagna is considered inauspicious for health. Therefore, you are advised to be cautious about health because Rahu gives health related tensions suddenly. Rahu in Lagna also makes one a soft target for black magic and evil eye and because of that even if one is absolutely fine health wise then also there remains the illusion of disease. After 9th September there shall be gradual improvement in health.</string>
    <string name="Leo_Career">The first half of the year appears to be excellent for your career making expeditions but you have to work very hard for getting desired success. Keep your will power and confidence intact. Those students who are inclined towards technical education are likely to make big achievement in their area of work.</string>
    <string name="Leo_Travel">This is not a highly favorable year for your journeys. Only short journeys are indicated. Those staying away from their motherland are likely to get an opportunity to travel to their native place. By the year end you shall be travelling to place of pilgrimage.</string>
    <!--<string name="Leo_Religiousdeed">You might take interest in occult and Tantra as there will be influence of saturn and Rahu on 5th house. 1. Donate articles made of iron to poor people on Saturday. 2. Serve red color cow. 3. Offer water to Sun daily.</string>-->






    <string name="Virgo_health">There shall be situation of ups and downs on professional front however you shall go on striving for the consolidation of your professional life. You might face troubles on professional front or else might get transferred to a place against your choice. The latter half of the year shall be auspicious. You would gain reputation and status with your hard work. Those doing job can expect promotion and betterment in their status. They shall get support, affection and respect from their seniors.</string>
    <string name="Virgo_wealth">Financial condition would be very good in this year. Your income and saving potential shall increase. There shall be sudden financial gains. The aspect of Jupiter on 5th house is giving strong indications of benefits from speculation, lottery etc too. After 12th September your money might get spent on the purchase of domestic articles and the aspect of Saturn on 10th house indicates expenditure on the health of father.</string>
    <!--<string name="Virgo_work">This year shall not be auspicious for your family life in the first half of it however, the latter half shall be auspicious. The transit of Saturn on 4th house indicates home and family life related tensions and as a result of it there shall be sudden eruption of difference of opinion with family members and you might have to move away from your place because of some work/business etc. After 12th September there would be betterment in family life and atmosphere.</string>-->
    <string name="Virgo_family">Those who do not have children can expect child birth in their family. This year is promising for the destiny of your children. Your bonding with your children shall grow stronger and sweet as a result of which family atmosphere would improve. The latter half of the year is giving indications of progress in the career of your children therefore progress and new employment can also be expected. There would be progress in the education of your children.</string>
    <string name="Virgo_children">his year is favorable for your health. The transit of Jupiter shall bring improvement in your health. If because of some reason you become victim of some kind of health trouble then it shall get cured quickly. There shall be improvement in health, your working efficiency shall increase and you would take interest in Yoga, meditation, exercise and other spiritual practices which would prove auspicious for your personality development, immunity and confidence.</string>
    <string name="Virgo_career">The favorable transit effect on house of education indicates success in competitive examinations and you shall be doing better in banking industry, management or any other educational pursuit which would prove to beneficial for career related progress like getting employment or making more gains. The latter half of the year i.e. after 12th September is auspicious for getting employment. Keep your confidence intact.</string>
    <string name="Virgo_travel">This year is auspicious for foreign journeys. The 12th house Rahu indicates sudden journeys. You might go on foreign journeys for the expansion of your work/business or up gradation of education or might get transferred to a place of choice.</string>
    <!--<string name="Virgo_religiousdeed">The first half of the year is more auspicious for going on pilgrimage. The aspect of Jupiter on 5th house is giving strong indications of religious inclination. You would be engaged in religious activities like Yagya, Anushthaan, Havan etc. 1. Grow a Tulsi(basil leave) plant at your home and worship it daily and light a lamp in the evening. 2. Get up before sun rise and offer water to Sun daily. 3. Light a lamp during your Puja.</string>-->







    <string name="Scorpio_health">This year is going to be excellent for professional life. Sudden rise in professional life is indicated. New business opportunities and financial gains in abundance are indicated but partnership venture shall yield average results. Those doing job are likely to get transferred. Develop good relations with seniors, powerful people and officers.</string>
    <string name="Scorpio_wealth">Financial condition would not be very good in this year. There shall be financial gains but scarcity of funds shall prevail and you are advised not to make any big investment. If necessary then make investment sensibly. The latter half of the year shall be favorable and there shall be probability of gain of paternal property and vehicle etc.</string>
    <!--<string name="Scorpio_work" tools:ignore="StringEscaping">This year shall not be very auspicious for your family life. Abstain from difference of opinion with family members as Saturn's transit is not auspicious for family life. Take care of health of spouse, father and siblings. The transit of Rahu and Saturn indicates worries related to parents and the probability of some kind of distance or difference of opinion with parents can also not be ruled out. You are advised to have control on your language otherwise situation might get deteriorated. It would be better to maintain patience while facing difficult and opposite situations.</string>-->
    <string name="Scorpio_family">The first half of the year is more auspicious for the progress of your children. There are indications of child birth too. Those who do not have children can expect child birth in their family in the first half of the year. Bonding with your children shall get strengthened. Children shall be interested in education but after 12th September they might face health troubles.</string>
    <string name="Scorpio_children">This would be an average year for your health. At times there won\'t be any health problem but the illusion of some disease would be chasing you. Take healthy diet, keep yourself relaxed and have lot of rest. Don\'t be careless about your health and do exercise on regular basis otherwise your health might get deteriorated. There might remain mental tensions because of domestic reasons. By year end there shall be substantial improvement on all fronts.</string>
    <string name="Scorpio_career">This would prove to be generally auspicious year for your career and success in competitive examinations. You would be able to make any type of achievement in your higher education. Therefore you are advised to work very hard for the accomplishment of your ambitions. Planetary transit is indicating enrolment in a professional degree course. In the latter part of the year you might not take much interest in your studies.</string>
    <string name="Scorpio_travel">This is not a highly favorable year for your journeys. Only short journeys are indicated. There are possibilities of your going on short journeys but long journeys are not indicated. By the year end you shall be travelling to place of pilgrimage. Students might get opportunity to go abroad for higher education in the latter half of the year. Those in job are likely to get transferred with promotion.</string>
    <!--<string name="Scorpio_religiousdeed">In the first half of the year you would be taking interest in religious activities and some religious Anushthaan and auspicious ceremonies would be performed in your family. You would be devoted to God and eventually might take interest in activities like meditation, yagya, mantra chanting and Bhagwat Katha etc. 1. Distribute Laddus on Thursday. 2. Observe fast on Thursdays and observe silence and stay away from non-vegetarianism and alcoholism. 3. Offer water to Peepal tree in the morning and light a lamp in the evening. 4. Chant \"Om Gang GanpatyeNamah\" Mantra on Wednesday in front of an idol of Lord Ganesha"</string>-->







    <string name="Libra_health">This year is auspicious for business. New business opportunities or job change chances with financial gains in abundance are indicated. Your enhanced confidence shall help you do better. Your adversaries shall try to create obstacles and difficulties for you. After 12th September the transit of Jupiter would be yielding highly auspicious results as a result of which you would be enjoying the cooperation and support of your seniors. The experienced people shall sharpen your working efficiency. If you are in partnership business you can expect more gains.</string>
    <string name="Libra_wealth">Financial condition would be good in this year. If you shall be striving sincerely then financial position shall get consolidated certainly. The inflow of money shall remain intact. Money would get spent on the celebration of some auspicious ceremony in family. In addition to that your some money shall go in curing the health troubles of family members.</string>
    <!--<string name="Libra_work">This year shall be average for your family life. Abstain from difference of opinion with mother and other family members. Be patient, speak sensibly and look after your mother. There might remain mental tensions because of domestic issues. Your tolerance and patience shall solve everything. After 12th September there shall be an improvement in family atmosphere</string>-->
    <string name="Libra_family">The first half of the year is not very auspicious for your children. There is probability of difference of opinion with children in the first half of the year. In the field of education children have to face trivial difficulties in the first half. You are advised to look after their health. Those who do not have children can expect child birth in their family in the latter half of the year i.e. after 12th September. Your bonding with your children shall grow better and the time period is more auspicious for the progress of your children.</string>
    <string name="Libra_children">The first half of the year shall be auspicious for your health but there might remain few health troubles. If you become victim of some health trouble then it shall get recovered quickly. The aspect of Saturn on 5th house might give some stomach related problem. You need to give proper attention to your diet. Unnecessary travelling and burden of extra work shall keep giving you feeling of fatigue.</string>
    <string name="Libra_career">From career point of view this year would be average. Students are advised to be alert in terms of preparations for future competitive examinations. The hard work done during this time shall help them get better results in future. After the September 2017 there are chances of getting admission in a reputed educational institute.</string>
    <string name="Libra_travel">The time period in this year is auspicious for going on especially religious journeys. You might go on foreign journeys for the expansion of your work/business or up gradation of education or might get transferred to a place of choice.</string>
    <!--<string name="Libra_religiousdeed">In the first half of the year you shall be engaging yourself in religious activities like charity and going on pilgrimage. After 12th September the combined influence of aspect of Saturn and Jupiter on 9th house shall incline you towards Puja, Yagya and meditation etc. 1. Offer sweets to small girls on Friday. 2. Serve your elders, parents, saints and Gurus and get their blessings.</string>-->







    <string name="Sagittarius_health">This year shall bring in mixed results for professional life. There is probability of change of job/work. Probability of transfer can also not be ruled out. Do not invest big money in new business. If you do not have any option except starting then also you are advised not to be overenthusiastic in terms of action, aggression, decision making and investment. Partnership business won\'t prove highly beneficial. After 12th September the planetary transit shall start yielding beneficial results and gradual improvement in business.</string>
    <string name="Sagittarius_wealth">Financial condition would be good in this year. The transit of Jupiter would prove to be beneficial for you financial gains and you would also get your blocked payments. There shall be an increase in your income and you might get rid of your old debts. You would be able to purchase landed property or house etc in this year. The latter half of the year indicates expenditure on the celebration of auspicious ceremony in the family.</string>
    <!--<string name="Sagittarius_work">This year shall be auspicious for your family life. The aspect of Jupiter on second house shall create an atmosphere of love, laughter, harmony and prosperity in the family. You shall be getting the cooperation of all family members. Some new member shall get added in the number of family members. If you are unmarried then you are likely to get married and the relationship with elder brother shall improve certainly. The time period is auspicious for his progress too. Legal issues in the family shall get resolved. You need to take care of the health of your spouse.</string>-->
    <string name="Sagittarius_family">This year is very auspicious for children and you can expect to get their cooperation. It is beneficial for the happiness, education, health, marriage and career of children. The latter half of the year is very auspicious for those who are expecting the birth of child in their family. Children shall be more interested in their studies and they are likely to get married.</string>
    <string name="Sagittarius_children">This would not be a great year for your health. The transit of Saturn is giving indications of stress and mental tensions. You also might have troubles like joint pain, headache and wind diseases. Therefore you need to be cautious about their health. Interest in Yoga, meditation and Ayurveda etc shall help.</string>
    <string name="Sagittarius_career">This year is good for for getting success in career. If you started some new work then you would be successful in that with an increase in your influence. Jupiter in transit in 10th house from your Rashi is favorable for pursuing some professional course. You might choose subjects like technical education, science, computers or language etc. The latter half of the year would prove good for doing well educationally and creating some source of income too. The latter half is also auspicious for being successful in competitive examinations.</string>
    <string name="Sagittarius_travel">There are no possibilities of change of place or going on journeys in the first half of the year. Saturn\'s transit is indicating obstacles and troubles related to journeys so be cautious. Those doing job are likely to get transferred in the latter half of the year.</string>
    <!--<string name="Sagittarius_religiousdeed">Because of the transit of Saturn in Lagna and that of Rahu in 9th house you would be taking interest in occult, Mantra Siddhi, and Tantra etc. You would be inclined towards your IshtaDevta in the latter half of the year. 1. Donate articles of copper and iron to poor people on Saturday. 2. Donate black blankets to poor people. 3. Do Abhishekam of Lord Shiva.</string>-->








    <string name="Pisces_health">The first half of the year is giving indications of its being auspicious for those doing business therefore; you shall be successful in your professional life with your hard work and destiny. The transit of jupiter in 7th house is giving indications of progress in business. Those doing job are likely to get transferred. This transfer would be very beneficial for them. After 12th September the time period won\'t be very favorable and the partnership venture might prove to be frustrating during that time.</string>
    <string name="Pisces_wealth">Financial condition would not be very good in the first half of this year. There shall be difficulties in financial gains in the first half of the year and in addition to that you won\'t be able to get your blocked money. Money shall get spent on the treatment of health troubles. It shall be essential to be cautious in terms of investment. Don\'t invest big money in that business or venture or in any other thing where some kind of risk is involved otherwise you are likely to lose your money. After 12th September the transit of jupiter shall prove favorable for financial matters. The aspect of jupiter on second house shall improve your financial position gradually. If you start any new business then it would prove beneficial for you. You shall become cooperative in your behavior because of which it shall be easier for you to make money.</string>
    <!--<string name="Pisces_work">his year shall be auspicious for your family life. The transit of Jupiter on 7th house indicates that the atmosphere of love, laughter, peace and harmony in the family shall remain intact especially with the support of your spouse and siblings. There might remain difference of opinion with parents or else you shall be worried about them or there might remain some kind of distance between you and them.</string>-->
    <string name="Pisces_family">his is going to turn out to be an auspicious year for your children. They shall be interested in education and succeed in accomplishing their goal.You shall also be happy with the progress of your children. In the latter half of the year i.e. after 9th September your children shall be facing lot of problems, tensions and obstacles. There can remain obstacles in the progress of your children. There are probabilities of miscarriage. It is not a good time for conceiving. The pregnant ladies are advised to wear cat\'s eye for the protection of pregnancy.</string>
    <string name="Pisces_children">This year is auspicious for your health. You shall succeed in improving your health and working efficiency. You shall get recovered quickly if you happen to become victim of some trivial health troubles. This year you are likely to get rid of you are already suffering from some old illness. After 12th September you shall have to be cautious from stomach disorders for that be disciplined in your eating habits.</string>
    <string name="Pisces_career">It would prove to be a beneficial year for career, education and competitive examination in the first half of it. There are possibilities of getting employment and those who are targeting bigger ambitions would be happy with the employment of their ambitions. The areas like medical science technology and commerce are sectors of growth for you. Those who are associated with these sectors or the profession of lawyer, judge or any other legal activity would get benefited from the planetary transit. After 9th September you are likely to face obstacles in your educational progress.</string>
    <string name="Pisces_travel">This year is auspicious for going on journeys. You shall go on long, short and foreign journeys. These journeys shall prove beneficial for students and business persons too. Those trying for transfer would get transferred to their place of choice.</string>
    <!--<string name="Pisces_religiousdeed">In the beginning of the year you would be interested in spiritual activities like Puja, Yagya and Anushthaan etc. Shiv Puja would be more beneficial. 1. Put a mark of Kesar and Ashtagandha. 2. Donate bananas and yellow sweets in a temple and distribute among poor people. 3. Donate useful article of iron on Saturday.</string>-->
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    <string name="Aquaris_health">You shall attain progress with your destiny and hard work. The transit of Rahu on 7th house is giving indications of change in business. This change won\'t be very favorable so avoid making of such change. During this time you are advised not to start any new work. You shall get recognition, progress and happiness in a place away from your birth place. Those doing job are likely to get transferred to a place not preferred. In the latter half of the year you shall be getting cooperation and guidance of experienced person because of which you can expect rise and gains. Abstain from getting into any legal issue and abstain from signing any important document carelessly</string>
    <string name="Aquaris_wealth">Financial condition would be very good in this year. There shall be an increase in your income and your saving potential shall improve. You shall be getting new sources of income. You would be gaining support from the senior people of your family. You need not put in lot of efforts to get back your blocked money. Some part of your money shall also get spent essentially on the improvement of your health. Don\'t make big investment in the latter part of the year.</string>
    <!--<string name="Aquaris_work">This year shall be good for your family life in the first half of it. There shall be an atmosphere of love, laughter, peace and harmony in the family. You might get cooperation of all family members especially from your mother. Those who are unmarried are likely to get married. Newly married people can expect the birth of a baby. In the latter half of the year you need to look after the health of your spouse.</string>-->
    <string name="Aquaris_family">The health, happiness, education and progress of children might get affected in the first half of the year therefore you need to put them on right track by giving them right type of guidance. The latter half of the year i.e. after 12th September the time period is very auspicious for those who are expecting the birth of child in their family. Betterment in the health, happiness, education and destiny of your children can be expected.</string>
    <string name="Aquaris_children">This would not be a great year for your health. The transit of Saturn and Rahu is giving indications of continuous intervention of diseases, stress and mental tensions. At times when you shall be fit there might remain illusion of disease. For enhancing your physical fitness you are advised to pay attention to your diet and life style. If you are already suffering from some health problem then you are advised to be extra cautious now. Disciplined life style, care and regular exercise is needed.</string>
    <string name="Aquaris_career">The first half of this year is average for your career and education. This is not a very favorable time for competitive aspirants. The chances of success in competitive examination shall get enhanced after 9th September. Therefore keep your will power and continuity in work intact. This will make you certainly successful. Those seeking technical education would be attaining special achievement and reputation in their organization.</string>
    <string name="Aquaris_travel">This is going to prove an inauspicious year for your journeys. There shall be obstacles in foreign journey however short journeys in the latter half including religious journeys especially after 12th September would be there in the latter half of the year. Those in job might get transferred to a place away from their birth place.</string>
    <!--<string name="Aquaris_religiousdeed" tools:ignore="StringEscaping">Jupiter would remain in 8th house till 12th September because of which you might fail to take required interest in religious activities. You won't be able to involve yourself in religious activities because of lack of concentration. After 12th September you would be able to take interest in religious activities like devotion to Guru, God, AkhandRamayanPaath and Bhagwat Katha etc. 1. Do Tula Daan i.e. donate wheat equivalent to your body weight. 2. Rotate a coconut on your head 7 times on Saturday and throw it in running water. 3. Serve your elders, seniors, parents, saints and gurus and get their blessings.</string>-->












    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
